<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Marcos Cannabrava RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Software Engineer]]></description><link>https://cannabrava.co</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 05:30:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Quotes]]></title><description><![CDATA[Simplicity vs Complexity Controlling complexity is the essence of computer programming. — Brian Wilson Kernighan Optimization hinders…]]></description><link>https://cannabrava.co/quotes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cannabrava.co/quotes/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Simplicity vs Complexity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Controlling complexity is the essence of computer programming.&lt;br&gt;
— Brian Wilson Kernighan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optimization hinders evolution. Everything should be built top-down, except the first time. Simplicity does not precede complexity, but follows it.&lt;br&gt;
— Alan Perlis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Entropy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A living organism [...] feeds upon negative entropy... Thus the device by which an organism maintains itself stationary at a fairly high level of orderliness (fairly low level of entropy) really consists in continually sucking orderliness from its environment.&lt;br&gt;
— Erwin Schrödinger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dying is very natural, staying alive is the miracle.&lt;br&gt;
— Jamshid Gharajedaghi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Risk&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reasonable man adapts himself to the world; the unreasonable one persists in trying to adapt the world to himself. Therefore, all progress depends on the unreasonable man.&lt;br&gt;
— George Bernard Shaw&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope is like a road in the country; there was never a road, but when many people walk on it, the road comes into existence.&lt;br&gt;
— Lu Xun&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Consciousness&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vedanta teaches that consciousness is singular, all happenings are played out in one universal consciousness and there is no multiplicity of selves.
[...]
Quantum physics thus [also] reveals a basic oneness of the universe.&lt;br&gt;
— Erwin Schrodinger&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The question of whether computers can think is just like the question of whether submarines can swim.&lt;br&gt;
— Edsger W. Dijkstra&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Visual Wittgenstein]]></title><description><![CDATA[models of reality 1 The world is everything that is the case. 2.0201 Every statement about complexes can be analyzed into a statement about…]]></description><link>https://cannabrava.co/philosophy/wittgenstein/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cannabrava.co/philosophy/wittgenstein/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;models of reality&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1 The world is everything that is the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.0201 Every statement about complexes can be analyzed into a statement about its constituent parts, and into those propositions which completely describe the complexes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.021 Objects form the substance of the world. Therefore they cannot be compound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: i.e. no dependencies, but &quot;can compose&quot; — the Democritus atom&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
      style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; max-width: 1194px; &quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/799341a18a598d363e55246939487114/187fa/wittgenstein.png&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
    style=&quot;padding-bottom: 36%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABQAAAAHCAYAAAAIy204AAAACXBIWXMAAAsTAAALEwEAmpwYAAABv0lEQVR42mVQz2sTQRjdgoi/qhKQHvS4EMglV8nFvyJnbzlEqlUveioo6En8B7x48FdRwYJCwYOgRVqbSNftxsa6bDZ2E7O7s7M7uzubyUw+JyOItA8e78338T0eo3me13Ac556P/FvDYHS9KNgNzpjUYinLsmsAMOPVH469GAS/F6W/InnTdb1LmoT0c9r/YIwZcggxScTt+3dhhMPZE4QQSvuDfWiZBqy3WxDgCD5+2RDD0AdC8i15fuJQKOdcBQaETqyfNveTlKcs5+OJ4HLM/TDgO7bL11tbfEfuN83vbIQQJEnWrtVq89pBkJR0QpIDZX8rEcoBU6EoxPRf05V3b+GrZanyqgCKjMvLy8cWFrST1Wr1rIw6UqlUjmpPX6107jx8ALKOyAs2U2h3dmGvZ6ugPceGl2tr8GnbBA/F8GR1VZjdDmQZ/XaxXj9eKpVOn9f1C7qunyuXy/NaTvPuVJ3CdMK5Mo9fPIPnb14rPx6PYbb/sPkZjF0L6ISphnGSmvVG48yhP0QIP8IxIUGIBmGIhpKDCGMPRXh/5Ie/QhT18zTvt4xt1+p2e5QWDsLxwO6575vN5qkDgXN/AE7aj+XlBmnkAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
  &gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;img
        class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
        alt=&quot;Wittgenstein&quot;
        title=&quot;&quot;
        src=&quot;/static/799341a18a598d363e55246939487114/187fa/wittgenstein.png&quot;
        srcset=&quot;/static/799341a18a598d363e55246939487114/5a46d/wittgenstein.png 300w,
/static/799341a18a598d363e55246939487114/0a47e/wittgenstein.png 600w,
/static/799341a18a598d363e55246939487114/187fa/wittgenstein.png 1194w&quot;
        sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1194px) 100vw, 1194px&quot;
        style=&quot;width:100%;height:100%;margin:0;vertical-align:middle;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;&quot;
        loading=&quot;lazy&quot;
        decoding=&quot;async&quot;
      /&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.202 The picture represents a possible state of affairs in the logical space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.225 There is no picture which is &lt;em&gt;a priori&lt;/em&gt; true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lesswrong.com/posts/KJ9MFBPwXGwNpadf2/skill-the-map-is-not-the-territory&quot;&gt;The Map is Not the Territory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.02 [...] What is thinkable is also possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: Was LW a techno-optimist? :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.11 We use the perceptible sign (sound or written sign, etc) of the proposition as a projections of the possible state of affairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: So we come full-circle. From reality is derived the model, which through language makes it way back into reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.3 Only the proposition has sense; only in the context of a proposition has a name meaning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;interlude: cruft, bloat, complexity&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.34 A proposition possesses essential and accidental features.
&lt;br/&gt;
Accidental are the features which are due to a particular way of producing the propositional sign. Essential are those which alone enable the proposition to express its sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.341 The essential in a proposition is therefore that which is common to all propositions which can express the same sense.
&lt;br/&gt;
And in the same way in general the essential in a symbol is that which all symbols which can fulfil the same purpose have in common.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/No_Silver_Bullet&quot;&gt;No Silver Bullet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;domain models, bounded contexts&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.026 The meanings of the simple signs (the words) must be explained to us, if we are to understand them.
&lt;br/&gt;
But propositions are self-explanatory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: Code (modules) should be self-explanatory. Classes, objects, variables, not necessarily.
The whole of a domain — a publicly exposed API — should be of an &quot;intuitive&quot;, self-explanatory nature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.03 [...] The proposition communicates to us a state of affairs, therefore it must be essentially connected with the state of affairs. [...]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.06 Propositions can be true or false only by being pictures of the reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;logic&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 Propositions are truth-functions of elementary propositions.
&lt;br/&gt;
(An elementary proposition is a truth-function of itself.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;epistemology&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.551 Our fundamental principle is that &lt;strong&gt;every question which can be decided at all by logic can be decided off-hand&lt;/strong&gt;.
&lt;br/&gt;
(And &lt;strong&gt;if we get into a situation where we need to answer such a problem by looking at the world, this shows that we are on a fundamentally wrong track.&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.6 &lt;strong&gt;The limits of my language mean the limits of my world.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: banger 💥&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.13 Logic is not a theory but a reflection of the world.
&lt;br/&gt;
Logic is transcendental.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.2 Mathematics is a logical method.
&lt;br/&gt;
The propositions of mathematics are equations, and therefore pseudo-propositions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.3 Logical research means the investigation of all regularity. And outside logic all is accident.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.373 The world is independent of my will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.421 It is clear that ethics cannot be expressed.
&lt;br/&gt;
Ethics is transcendental.
&lt;br/&gt;
(Ethics and aesthetics are one.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: we can sense a turn of events coming...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;take a big breath&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.4311 Death is not an event of life. Death is not lived through.
&lt;br/&gt;
If by eternity is understood not endless temporal duration but timelessness, then he lives eternally who lives in the present.
&lt;br/&gt;
Our life is endless in the way that our visual field is without limit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: WTF. How did we get here?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.4312 The temporal immortality of the human soul, that is to say, its eternal survival after death, is not only in no way guaranteed, but this assumption in the first place will not do for us what we always tried to make it do. Is a riddle solved by the fact that I survive for ever? Is this eternal life not as enigmatic as our present one? The solution of the riddle of life in space and time lies outside space and time.
&lt;br/&gt;
(It is not problems of natural science which have to be solved.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: 🤯&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.4321 The facts all belong only to the task and not to its performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: 🍄&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.5 For an answer which cannot be expressed the question too cannot be expressed.
&lt;br/&gt;
The riddle does not exist.
&lt;br/&gt;
If a question can be put at all, then it can also be answered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.51 [...] For doubt can only exist where there is a question; a question only where there is an answer, and this only where something can be said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: 🤔&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.52 We feel that &lt;strong&gt;even if all possible scientific questions be answered, the problems of life have still not been touched at all. Of course there is then no question left, and just this is the answer&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.521 &lt;strong&gt;The solution of the problem of life is seen in the vanishing of this problem.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
(Is not this the reason why men to whom after long doubting the sense of life became clear, could not then say wherein this sense consisted?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.522 There is indeed the inexpressible. This shows itself; it is the mystical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.53 &lt;strong&gt;The right method of philosophy would be this. To say nothing except what can be said&lt;/strong&gt;, i.e. the propositions of natural science, i.e. something that has nothing to do with philosophy: and then always, when someone else wished to say something metaphysical, to demonstrate to him that he had given no meaning to certain signs in his propositions. &lt;strong&gt;This method would be unsatisfying to the other&lt;/strong&gt; — he would not have the feeling that we were teaching him philosophy — but it would be the only strictly correct method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: lol 🤣&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.54 My propositions are elucidatory in this way: he who understands me finally recognizes them as senseless, when he has climbed out through them, on them, over them. (He must so to speak throw away the ladder, after he has climbed up on it.)
&lt;br/&gt;
He must surmount these propositions; then he sees the world rightly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7 &lt;strong&gt;Whereof one cannot speak, thereof one must be silent.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MC: dropping the mic with this one he closes the book&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wittgenstein for programmers Language, Logic, Epistemology Visual Tractatus Logico-Philosophicus Stoicism The useful Philosophy Seneca's "On…]]></description><link>https://cannabrava.co/philosophy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cannabrava.co/philosophy/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;wittgenstein&quot;&gt;Wittgenstein for programmers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Language, Logic, Epistemology&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;wittgenstein&quot;&gt;Visual Tractatus Logico-Philosophicus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;stoicism&quot;&gt;Stoicism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The useful Philosophy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;stoicism&quot;&gt;Seneca&apos;s &quot;On The Shortness of Life&quot;, Marcus Aurelius&apos; &quot;Meditations&quot;, and Epictetus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stoicism]]></title><description><![CDATA[Marcus Aurelius The Philosopher-King, the last of the Five Good Emperors. The happiness of your life depends upon the quality of your…]]></description><link>https://cannabrava.co/philosophy/stoicism/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cannabrava.co/philosophy/stoicism/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;Marcus Aurelius&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Philosopher-King, the last of the Five Good Emperors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The happiness of your life depends upon the quality of your thoughts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If it is not right, do not do it. If it is not true, do not say it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Waste no more time arguing about what a good man should be. Be one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What doesn&apos;t transmit light creates its own darkness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your three components: body, breath, mind. Two are yours in trust; to the third alone you have clear title.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Seneca&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rich philosopher who preached the virtues of the poor. Some call it hypocrisy, others (N. N. Taleb), the first Antifragile mindset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;But what if poverty is something to be desired? Riches have shut off many a man from the attainment of wisdom; poverty is unburdened and free from care. When the trumpet sounds, the poor man knows that he is not being attacked; when there is a cry of &quot;Fire,&quot; he only seeks a way of escape, and does not ask what he can save.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is not the man who has too little that is poor, but the one who hankers after more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will always be causes for anxiety, whether due to prosperity or to wretchedness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In guarding their fortune men are often closefisted, yet, when it comes to the matter of wasting time, in the case of the one thing in which it is right to be miserly, they show themselves most extravagant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Happy the man who improves other people not merely when he is in their presence but even when he is in their thoughts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We must indulge the mind and from time to time allow it the leisure which is its food and strength. We must go for walks out of doors, so that the mind can be strengthened and invigorated by a clear sky and plenty of fresh air. At times it will acquire fresh energy from a journey by carriage and a change of scene, or from socializing and drinking freely. Occasionally we should even come to the point of intoxication, sinking into drink but not being totally flooded by it; for it does wash away cares, and stirs the mind to its depths, and heals sorrow just as it heals certain diseases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Epictetus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If a person speaks ill of you, do not make excuses, but answer: &quot;He was ignorant of my other faults, else he would&apos;ve mentioned those as well.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you wish to be a writer, write.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The world turns aside to let any man pass who knows where he is going.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First learn the meaning of what you say, and then speak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you want to improve, be content to be thought foolish and stupid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Circumstances don&apos;t make the man, they only reveal him to himself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&apos;t just say you have read books. Show that through them you have learned to think better, to be a more discriminating and reflective person. Books are the training weights of the mind. They are very helpful, but it would be a bad mistake to suppose that one has made progress simply by having internalized their contents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title><description><![CDATA[surfing surfing
Sumbawa, Indonesia... more on Instagram books A Man's Search for Meaning by Viktor Frankl Gödel, Escher, Bach: An Eternal…]]></description><link>https://cannabrava.co/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://cannabrava.co/hello-world/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h4&gt;surfing&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://res.cloudinary.com/mpc-cloud/image/upload/c_scale,w_1808/v1585134904/marcoscannabrava_github/surf_rbypcn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;surfing&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Sumbawa, Indonesia... more on Instagram&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;books&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Man&apos;s Search for Meaning by Viktor Frankl&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gödel, Escher, Bach: An Eternal Golden Braid by Douglas Hofstadter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Almanack of Naval Ravikant: A Guide to Wealth and Happiness by Eric Jorgenson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anything by Eliyahu Goldratt, Charlie Munger, Nassim Taleb, Jorge Luis Borges, or Garcia Marquez&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What Is Life? by Erwin Schrödinger&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High Output Management by Andy Grove&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Benjamin Franklin: An American Life by Walter Isaacson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Beginning of Infinity by David Deutsch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Mind at Play: How Claude Shannon Invented the Information Age by Jimmy Soni&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;software&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing Data-Intensive Applications by Martin Kleppmann&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code That Fits in Your Head: Heuristics for Software Engineering by Mark Seemann&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working Effectively with Legacy Code by Michael C. Feathers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Art of UNIX Programming by Eric S. Raymond&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Software Engineering at Google: Lessons Learned from Programming Over Time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;sci-fi&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Last Question by Asimov&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bobiverse series by Dennis Taylor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 Body Problem by Liu Cixin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anything by Ted Chiang, Ken Liu, or Greg Egan
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;but these in particular slap
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&quot;Crystal Nights&quot; by GE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&quot;Story of your Life&quot; and &quot;Anxiety Is the Dizziness of Freedom&quot; by TC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&quot;Pantheon&quot; (animated series based on some of KL stories)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;investing&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Intelligent Investor by Benjamin Graham&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Margin of Safety by Seth A. Klarman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;music&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Genre&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Artists&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Synthwave&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/5bQ1u5yLlL2WZv49doSgRz&quot;&gt;Hotel Pools&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/3gi5McAv9c0qTjJ5jSmbL0&quot;&gt;A.L.I.S.O.N&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/2exebQUDoIoT0dXA8BcN1P&quot;&gt;Home&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/2UuvaSzB0VNumArR71ReMT&quot;&gt;Emil Rottmayer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/5p9HO3XC5P3BLxJs5Mtrhm&quot;&gt;Djo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Lofi&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/6N4HlHINMvoTyAL0yhBUCk&quot;&gt;Saib&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/1EJzWKVDeysgbyuZGfEFde&quot;&gt;The Deli&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/5b0XQwyoJBFd3MwL2YxEPO&quot;&gt;Nohidea&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/73aKnLT4O8G2pBEfdlQzrE&quot;&gt;Purrple Cat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Other&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/1xU878Z1QtBldR7ru9owdU&quot;&gt;Phoenix&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/10tysauSA5JATqniBDu2Ed&quot;&gt;The Dodos&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/0oeUpvxWsC8bWS6SnpU8b9&quot;&gt;The Naked And Famous&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/41AbNVba2ccpmcc9QtOJE7&quot;&gt;Kings Of Convenience&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/1O10apSOoAPjOu6UhUNmeI&quot;&gt;SBTRKT&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/21mKp7DqtSNHhCAU2ugvUw&quot;&gt;ODESZA&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/6nxWCVXbOlEVRexSbLsTer&quot;&gt;Flume&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/4PhdYoQGH8s1xee81dqQOO&quot;&gt;Natiruts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/2nB77EV6Al8aHXfxa6YfrW&quot;&gt;Bossacucanova&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/77ZUbcdoU5KCPHNUl8bgQy&quot;&gt;João Gilberto&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/5JYtpnUKxAzXfHEYpOeeit&quot;&gt;Jorge Ben Jor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Geniuses&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;JS Bach, Koji Kondo, Hans Zimmer&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>